<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animals</string>
    <string name="vacuna_btn">Vaccines</string>
    <string name="pet_raza">Breed:</string>
    <string name="nota_btn">Notes</string>
    <string name="pet_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="modif_btn">Modify</string>
    <string name="menu_pets">Pets</string>
    <string name="menu_map">Map</string>
    <string name="pet_genero">Gender:</string>
    <string name="menu_contac">Contacts</string>
    <string name="menu_archivo">Animal Rights</string>
    <string name="cancelar_btn">Cancel</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Animals</string>
    <string name="pet_tipo">Animal:</string>
    <string name="menu_ajustes">Settings</string>
    <string name="aceptar_btn">Accept</string>
    <string name="pet_birth">Birth Date:</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="art9">Article 9</string>
    <string name="art8">Article 8</string>
    <string name="art7">Article 7</string>
    <string name="art6">Article 6</string>
    <string name="art5">Article 5</string>
    <string name="art4">Article 4</string>
    <string name="art3">Article 3</string>
    <string name="art2">Article 2</string>
    <string name="art14">Article 14</string>
    <string name="art13">Article 13</string>
    <string name="art12">Article 12</string>
    <string name="art11">Article 11</string>
    <string name="art10">Article 10</string>
    <string name="art1">Article 1</string>
    <string name="art13_a">A dead animal must be treated with respect.</string>
    <string name="art2_c">All animals have the right to the attention, care and protection of man.</string>
    <string name="art1_a">All animals are born equal to life and have the same rights to existence.</string>
    <string name="art2_a">Every animal has the right to be respected.</string>
    <string name="art4_a">Every animal belonging to a wild species has the right to live freely in its own natural terrestrial, aerial or aquatic environment and to reproduce.</string>
    <string name="art5_a">Every animal belonging to a species that traditionally lives in the environment of man, has the right to live and grow at the rhythm and in the conditions of life and freedom that are typical of its species.</string>
    <string name="art6_a">Every animal chosen by man as a companion has the right that the duration of its life is in accordance with its natural longevity.</string>
    <string name="art7_a">Every working animal has the right to a reasonable limitation of the time and intensity of work, to a restorative diet and to rest.</string>
    <string name="art11_a">Any act that involves the unnecessary death of an animal is a biocide, that is, a crime against life.</string>
    <string name="art12_a">Any act that involves the death of a large number of wild animals is genocide, that is, a crime against the species.</string>
    <string name="art4_b">Any deprivation of liberty, even that for educational purposes, is contrary to this right.</string>
    <string name="art5_b">Any modification of said rhythm or said conditions that was imposed by man, is contrary to said right.</string>
    <string name="art3_b">If the death of an animal is necessary, it must be instantaneous, painless and non-distressing.</string>
    <string name="art3_a">No animal will be subjected to mistreatment or cruel acts.</string>
    <string name="art10_a">No animal will be exploited for the amusement of man.</string>
    <string name="art14_a">The organisms for the protection and safeguarding of animals must be represented at the governmental level.</string>
    <string name="art14_b">The rights of the animal must be defended by law, as well as the rights of man.</string>
    <string name="art9_a">Animals raised for food should be fed, housed, transported and slaughtered without causing them anxiety or pain.</string>
    <string name="art8_b">Alternative experimentation techniques must be used and developed.</string>
    <string name="art10_b">Animal exhibits and shows that use them are incompatible with the dignity of the animal.</string>
    <string name="art13_b">Violent scenes in which there are animal victims should be prohibited in the cinema and on television, unless their objective is to denounce the attacks against animal rights.</string>
    <string name="art8_a">Animal experimentation that involves physical or psychological suffering is incompatible with animal rights, whether it be medical, scientific, commercial experiments, or any other form of experimentation.</string>
    <string name="art12_b">Pollution and destruction of the natural environment lead to genocide.</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Pet Management And More</string>
    <string name="art2_b">Man, as an animal species, cannot claim the right to exterminate other animals or exploit them in violation of his right. You have the obligation to put your knowledge at the service of animals.</string>
    <string name="art6_b">The abandonment of an animal is a cruel and degrading act.</string>
    <string name="lenguaje_btn">Languaje</string>
    <string name="str_en">English</string>
    <string name="str_es">Spanish</string>
    <string name="title_Idiomas">Select your Language</string>
    <string name="idiomasDialog">English Or Spanish?</string>
    <string name="txtContactos">Emergency Contacts</string>
    <string name="btnAtras">Back</string>
    <string name="txtNota">Note</string>
</resources>